♪No one left to lean on♪
♪No way out, no place to run♪
♪Tears held back inside my eyes♪
♪I run against the wind and time♪
♪Loved and lost, regrets remain♪
♪But tears fall down like gentle rain♪
♪I look up strong, I grow with pride♪
♪Living life with heart untied♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪Break through the noise,
let them hear me♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪Break through the noise,
let them hear me♪
=Dragon King's Decree=
=Episode 10=
The Sacred Ancestor's birthday
is approaching.
(Luo Weijie, the Serpents' Leader)
Are the sacrifices ready?
Chief Luo,
we always offer young girls
during the Sacred Ancestor's birthday.
We don't have girls
who fit the criteria
in the village anymore.
Besides,
must we continue
(Zhang Lingling, Elder of the Serpents)
such a wicked tradition?
How dare you!
Offering young girls
to the Sacred Ancestor
is the only way to protect us!
Elder Zhang,
you have repeatedly raised objections.
Are you trying to rebel?
The clan is already short of women.
If this goes on,
the clan will become extinct!
You!
Elder Zhang,
you worry the clan
will have no more women,
but are you not afraid
of the Sacred Ancestor's wrath
that could wipe the clan out?
Since
we can't find a suitable sacrifice,
I think
we should follow custom.
Release the spirit.
It will decide.
Go.
The Sacred Ancestor's messenger.
Come in.
Don't be scared.
Mei, I'm here.
Give her to me.
Give her to me!
- No!
- Let go!
Give her to me!
I'm begging you!
If we don't give her up,
we all have to die!
Please!
It's our honor to offer her
to the Sacred Ancestor.
Mother.
- Thank you, Sacred Ancestor.
- Mei!
Farewell, Elder.
- Thank you.
- My daughter!
- Thank you, Elder.
What's the point
of protecting a home like this?
Elder Zhang,
our informant reported
that a outsider male
has fallen into our forest trap.
He's locked in the dungeon now.
Let's take a look.
I have questions.
Don't you shout.
Outsider,
why are you in the Serpents' territory?
I didn't intend to barge in.
We were just on our way to Wujing City
and merely passing through.
Merely passing through?
But I heard
someone caused a big disturbance
in the forest yesterday.
We were attacked in the forest
and had to defend ourselves.
He's a top assassin from Wujing,
and you escaped unscathed.
It's all thanks to my niece,
Feng Zhilou,
that we're still alive.
We got separated somehow,
and I stumbled into your trap.
Please.
Do you know where my niece
is right now?
You're from Feng Manor?
Yes.
Elder!
I have no ill intentions!
Find a time.
Elder!
(What's going on?)
An offering to sir.
Zhilou.
Chu Moshang.
What just happened?
The forest miasma causes people
to lose their senses
and fall into the nightmare
of their deepest fear.
I'm late.
Sorry I made you worry.
So you know you were late.
Why did you take so long?
You already have nine spiritual roots
and all sorts of weapons,
yet you still managed
to put yourself in danger.
Way to go.
Why're you mocking me again?
Uncle Qingyun's missing.
The miasma in this forest
is especially evil.
You'll fall into an illusion
if you're not careful.
I saw a group of girls
trapped together just now.
Chanting they were to be offered.
The Serpents have a mysterious cave
where a Sacred Ancestor
who's never shown his face resides.
He watches over this territory
which is why the Serpents
have been safe until now.
The miasma just now
was probably generated
to ward off enemies.
Young Master.
We finally found you.
Fei Yuan, Bai Lu,
look for Mr. Qingyun.
Yes.
Leave it to me!
Let's wait here for a moment.
When do you think the Young Master
will retrieve the sigil?
If he cant' bear to do it,
we can help him.
Young Master has his own plans.
It's not your place to interfere.
Mr. Qingyun!
I feel like you've changed
compared to before.
But I've always looked like this.
I'm not talking about your appearance.
It's that you...
look
more like human.
You sure know how to give praises.
What happened
to that brother of yours
who keeps trying
to kill you?
He has received his punishment.
I never knew
you were so articulate
in front of Father.
Moshang, what're you talking about?
I don't understand.
Father isn't here.
Drop the kind act.
If I hadn't
experienced your hatred myself,
and your talent for stabbing people
in the back,
I would really doubt
if my memory was flawed.
If you're envious,
try to be like me the next time
you make a mistake.
You still show no remorse
even now.
I was outmaneuvered this time.
I didn't expect someone
like Feng Zhilou to appear.
I just came to tell you
that no matter which of us
becomes the Dragon King,
you will always be my brother.
This
will never change.
Don't act
all high and mighty to lecture me.
In Father
and the whole clan's eyes,
I don't even have the right
to compete with you.
They only have eyes for you.
I don't need your pity,
and I certainly
don't need this brotherly affection.
So did you manage
to find the solution
to retrieve the sigil?
Kill Feng Zhilou.
Retrieve the sigil
and marry the Wujing Saintess.
This is all you can do
right now.
Young Master.
How is it?
Did you find my uncle?
Miss Zhilou,
we didn't see any signs of Mr. Qingyun.
But don't worry,
we didn't find traces
of struggle either.
Is someone there?
Save me.
Young Master,
there's a cry for help there.
Is someone there?
Where?
Please save me.
Save...
Save me.
Are you alright?
Don't be scared.
We won't hurt you.
What happened to you?
I...
was chosen as a sacrifice
to the Sacred Ancestor.
I just managed to escape.
Please.
Help us.
She has a veil.
She must be from the Serpents.
Us?
Are you saying
there are other girls?
Many of them are much younger than me.
They...
are still children
but have to be offered as well.
Why is that?
It's the Serpents' tradition.
At every birthday
of the Sacred Ancestor,
he...
he eats people.
What?
Could Mr. Qingyun have been eaten?
The Sacred Ancestor has a preference
and only eats young girls
chosen by the spirit
among the villagers.
Heavens.
Where's that wretched creature now?
In the cave behind the altar.
Let's go now.
It's...
terrifying there.
Don't you fear death?
Fei Yuan, Bai Lu,
send her home first.
Yes.
Leave it to me.
This way.
To be raised...
only for procreation
or to be fed
to the Sacred Ancestor.
This reminds me of the women
in the Feng Manor.
No freedom,
and at the mercy of others.
To me, this behavior
is akin to the Demons.
If that Sacred Ancestor
must use this method
to demonstrate his power,
then he is the evil incarnate.
This is unforgivable.
A lot have happened
after you left.
Father...
sacrificed himself
to save Feng Manor.
I want to look for Mother
in Wujing City,
but Uncle Qingyue
has gone missing.
I still want to save those girls,
but I don't know
what to do now.
Don't worry.
I'm right here with you.
The heavens might not
do anything for you,
but they will listen
to your most sincere prayers.
It'll be a miracle
if you manage to resolve the issue
with your brother.
I didn't mean to blame you for leaving.
What if...
I really am the Dragon God?
Just like you said.
The heavens might not
do anything for me,
so...
I should make myself stronger.
Besides,
you always show up immediately
whenever I'm in danger.
♪Like petals fall, gone with the clouds♪
♪Like stars fade fast in open skies♪
♪Like snowflakes melting softly
in the evening haze♪
♪Like your fleeting glance
that gave me one brief dream's grace♪
♪Like fireflies flicker
through wild grass, fleeting light♪
♪Like evening breeze
that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪Like fleeting thoughts
that surge and then unwind♪
♪Chance meetings fade,
just empty rooms left behind♪
♪You brought a wave
that stirred a wild, restless sea♪
♪Light as a feather,
yet it sank an island deep in me♪
♪In that one moment,
life's grip I couldn't break or sway♪
♪Leaving me lost in memories,
small and fading away♪